KARLY HOFFMAN



WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERTISE



FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

COPY WRITING

DESIGN

TECH SKILLS



JAVASCRIPT

HTML/CSS

П

NODE.JS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE



PROFILE

Web editor turned web developer. Gained experience writing and organizing content for web pages, now brings that content to life through programming. Has an eye for detail and the ability to add functionality to any page or application. Knowledgeable, dependable, and versatile in the web industry.



EXPERIENCE

WEB EDITOR DEC 2011 - AUG 2016

TENNIS WAREHOUSE Wrote in-depth product reviews. Created original descriptions for apparel featured on website. Contributed blog entries for the official Tennis Warehouse blog. Managed the Pinterest social media account. Assisted with writing and editing web content.

NEWS CONTRIBUTOR JAN 2016 - APRIL 2016

INDIE SHUFFLE Reported newsworthy music stories, which included breaking news, album releases, tour dates and interviews. Fact checked and referenced reliable sources. Coordinated with other contributors using a CMS to prevent duplicate articles. Ensured article formatting is consistent.

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN APRIL 2011 - JUNE 2011

NOLA LIGHT WORKS, **LLC** Designed promotional materials for company, including logos, flyers and postcards. Updated and managed company website.



EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE PROGRAM SEPT 2016 - DEC 2016

GENERAL ASSEMBLY Full time web development program which included 500+ hours of professional training over twelve weeks. Course topics included HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Ruby, Angular.js and SQL.

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE JULY 2007 - JUNE 2011

CALIFORNIA POLYTECHNIC STATE UNIVERSITY Majored in Recreation, Parks, and Tourism Administration with dual concentrations in Sport Management and Special Event Planning.



KARLYHOFFMAN@GMAIL.COM 760.533.0674 KARLYHOFFMAN.COM Based in Chicago, Il